of the time, not only most of the time, the area tools will not detect and remove the
armament tools automatically from the machine because the armament tools are a legitimate
application that will be widely used by the system administrators and many users inside
the organization. So, we cannot create detection tools to delete the armament tools from
the machine. We can add the hash of the armament tool in EDR or antivirus software database
to delete the armament tools if it was detected, if it was downloaded inside the environment.
So, that was not possible because armament tools are a legitimate application that will
be used by good things as well as for bad actors. And let us see, we can create a rule
for a armament tool if it was downloaded, it will only detect the applications like someone
downloaded the armament tool, someone using the armament tools like that. So, this is one
of the detection tools that we have created. So, I have given a lot of widely used arm tools
here. It will not remove the armament tools from the machine, but it will alert the
analyst same suspicious armament tool detector, someone using an armament tool. So, the armament
tool will be, it will not be terminated, it will be still in the machine, the user can
able to use the armament tool, but it will give an alert he is using an armament tool.
So, by this way, we can understand, we can call the user and we can ask why you are using
any desk, whether it was expected or not. So, any desk application was expected. So, if
the user said the unit is not expected, we can consider that as an active threat. So, this
is the only way we can create a behavior detection tool, someone using an armament tool,
we cannot able to static detections to delete the armament tool from the machine, because
it will delete, it will completely delete any desk, because any desk will be used by both
the side, the good thing and as well as the bad thing. So, with the only way, we can detect
the armament tool without deleting. So, once we confirm it with the user or who is an end user
or a customer, we can take a response action, appropriate that.
Let us hop off from here, I hope you have a clear understanding. So, this rule is nothing,
but here I have listed the armament tools and this rule is designed with the KQL language
in a KQL language and this device process events. If the armament tool was present in
any of the directory folder path, it will automatically detect the detect that and it
will give a lot to the analyst, who is working as a blue team. So, let us hop off from
here. We'll connect you guys in the next video. Bye bye!